the-black-angel.com 2018-01-13

# Privacy Notice - The Black Angel

## Privacy Notice

The Black Angel (which is owned and run by Supernova Cult S.A.R.L.) is an online shop designed to deliver the best possible experience to customers.

We appreciate your trust and are committed to protecting the privacy of all and any personal information we are required to gather during your interaction with our online shop.

You can browse our shop for gothic clothing and accessories in the safety of knowing that all your data is handled confidentially.

### Security & protection of personal information

We protect and security of your information by using a variety of best-practices and state-of-art technology for our online shop. All data you may enter during your purchase is encrypted and transmitted by secure sockets.

We work with one of the best hosting company of the US (Myhosting VPS), which guarantees the best possible security for your and our data. The servers that are storing your customer data are secured both physically and on software / hardware level, and we don't store any payment data of any kind.

We take your privacy very seriously, and the security measures of our gothic shop are designed to protect that information.

### No unsolicited emails or spam

We don’t share or sell personal information. Period. We don't divulge contact details from customer or from our mailing list. We are just as annoyed by spam as you are. And will never do anything that might result in you receiving unwanted emails after purchasing from us.

You'll only get one thing from us.

Which is what you ordered, gothic clothing and accessories by the best brands in goth fashion. Nothing else. No spam.

#### Information you give us

We receive and store any information you provide to us when you complete surveys, participate in a sweepstakes or other incentive, sign up to receive our newsletter or other email communications, communicate by email, telephone or physical mail with our customer service, or otherwise interact with us.

Such information may include your name, address, email address, shopping interests and preferences, transaction history, and other personal data.

You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to participate in our surveys or incentives or place orders should you not chose to provide the information necessary to process the transaction.

#### Information gathered automatically

When you interact with our website, we receive information, which might be temporarily stored. This is done through “cookies”, which helps to enhance your shopping experience in our store. This information is usually anonymous and contains statistical data, which helps us to improve our website's performance and ease of navigation.

When you add gothic clothing or accessories to your shopping cart on our website, these items and size combinations are temporarily stored in "cookies" in your browser, until checkout is complete, after which the cookie will be removed from your browser. Therefore having cookies enabled is required to make the online shop work on your computer.

### Emails policy

The Black Angel will only contact you in the context of your order when the processing requires us to do so (to confirm shipping or payment details, item availability, etc.).

We only send periodical newsletters or emails regarding important updates regarding our online shop, new goth clothing or our other major events to customers and subscribers who have signed up for email-updates.

This is a voluntary subscription that can be canceled any time. An unsubscribe link is contained in the confirmation email. If you have problems removing your email address from the list, please email contact our webmaster and we will manually remove your email from the list.

### Privacy release in case of legal investigation

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, enforce or apply our User Agreement and other agreements, assist in fraud protection or investigation, or protect the rights, property, and security of Supernova Cult S.A.R.L., our users, customers, or others.
